

ZUBAIR AHMED

FRONTEND DEVELOPER VIDEO EDITOR GRAPHIC DESIGNER

ABOUT ME_

I'm Zubair Ahmed — a seasoned creative professional with over 5 years of experience in video editing and graphic design.

I've expanded my creative journey into front-end development, combining my design sensibility with modern web technologies to craft responsive, intuitive, and engaging digital experiences.

CONTACT INFO

PHONE

+92 3266179272

EMAIL

zubi6349@gmail.com

AREA

Sodiwal, Band Road, Lahore, Pakistan.

LANGUAGES_

- English
- Urdu
- Punjabi

HOBBIES_







Gaming Reading

EXPERIENCE

Inkhorn Solutions/ Lahore

2020-2021

I have worked here as a graphic designer and 2d animator approximately for 1 years.

Vision Technologies/ Lahore

2023-2024

I have worked here as a senior graphic designer and sales executive for 1 year.

EXPERTISE

- Adobe Photoshop cc
- Adobe Illustrator cc
- Adobe InDesign
- Adobe After Effects cc
- Adobe Premiere Pro cc
- Adobe XD
- Adobe Audition
- Figma

- Video Editing
- Graphic Designing
- 2D Animation
- Web Design
- FrontEnd Development
- React JS
- CSS/Tailwind
- Javascript

EDUCATION_

I.C.S PHYSICS

Government Science College 2021-2023

GC FAISALABAD AFFILIATED (CONTINUED)